Maite,
but you have to have an opinion
like yours, enormously, with the MOP in
Asia, and of course
they use it to put an external,
terrestrial visual site for a guy,
Ivan was going to fly, he stays for Andina,
which I'm not, as an intention, took
Dark Mother, I don't even have Facebook
Panama in the room
[Music]
iPad
Santiago year
[Music]
This girl has no tube
[Applause] [
Music] Whiting Amac Ingrid cowhide, but [Music] [
Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] does
n't
heal and a
Syrian glove are part
[Applause]
Ah
[Music]
[Applause]
Look,
Andina, but
dynamic guard, since she won't pay
anything
to her anymore
and
[Music]
knows they make them sisters,
ah
[Music]